{
	"intro" : [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"random"			: 3,
			"dialog_rand1"		: "Seeing you has brought This Unit delight beyond all reasonable measure.",
			"dialog_rand2"		: "This Unit is experiencing levels of joy that are at risk for an overflow error.",
			"dialog_rand3"		: "This Unit can not handle the excitement levels that she is experiencing.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "You can tell by the expression on the face of This Unit.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "Will you be testing your knowledge today?",
		},
	],
	
	"op_round1"		: "Start the quiz",
	"op_round2"		: "Start Round Two",
	"op_round3"		: "Start The Final Round",
	"op_end"		: "End Quiz",
	"op_leave"		: "Leave",
	
	"round1_text"		: {
		"character"	: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
		"dialog"	: "Answer |C3|four questions correctly|C0|, without accruing |C3|three strikes,|C0| and This Unit will present you with a reward.",
	},
	"round2_text"		: {
		"character"	: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
		"dialog"	: "Answer |C3|four more questions correctly|C0| for another reward.|L|These questions will be more difficult.",
	},
	"round3_text"		: {
		"character"	: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
		"dialog"	: "Answer |C3|four more questions correctly|C0| for a final reward.|L|This will be the most difficult set.",
	},
	"end_text"		: {
		"character"	: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
		"dialog"	: "Are you tired of the quiz for today?",
	},
	"leave_text"		: {
		"character"	: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_sad"],
		"dialog"	: "You do not want to play today?",
	},
	"leave_confirm"		: {
		"character"	: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_upset"],
		"dialog"	: "Are you sure you must leave now?",
	},
	
	"reward_title"	: "Choose Reward",
	
	"comment_reward"	: {
		"character"	: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
		"dialog"	: "Choose one of these gifts to take.|L|There are no wrong answers here.",
	},
	"reward_confirm"	: {
		"character"	: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
		"dialog"	: "Will you take this gift?",
	},
	
	"correct_answer" : [
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "That is |C3|Correct!",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "[VAL1]",
		}
	],
	
	"incorrect_answer" : [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_sad"],
			"dialog"			: "That is |shake||C4|Incorrect.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_confused"],
			"dialog"			: "[VAL1]",
		}
	],
	
	"ask_question" : [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "[VAL1]",
		}
	],
	"first_question" : "|C3|First Question:|C0| [VAL1]",
	"next_question"  : "|C3|Question [VAL2]:|C0| [VAL1]",
	
	"default_correct_1"	: "This Unit is impressed.",
	"default_correct_2"	: "Your memory is impeccable.",
	"default_correct_3"	: "The joy value of This Unit has increased.",
	"default_correct_4"	: "Joy levels have increased.",
	"default_correct_5"	: "This Unit can detect your elation.",
	"default_correct_6"	: "Delight detected.",
	"default_correct_7"	: "Satisfaction ensues.",
	"default_correct_8"	: "A pleasurable outcome.",
	
	"default_incorrect_1"	: "Joy levels have decreased.",
	"default_incorrect_2"	: "You may take a moment to grieve.",
	"default_incorrect_3"	: "This Unit can detect your grief.",
	"default_incorrect_4"	: "This Unit made that one too difficult.",
	
	"correct_senti_1"	: "It makes This Unit so happy that you know so much about her.",
	"correct_senti_2"	: "Only a true friend would know that much about This Unit.",
	"correct_senti_3"	: "You knowing This Unit so well sends her joy value into orbit.",
	"wrong_sentinel"	: "This Unit had hoped that you would remember this much about her, but she forgives you.",
	"battle_sentinel"	: "It was a most thrilling battle with This Unit, was it not?",
	"forgot_sentinel"	: "Is This Unit really that forgettable?",
	"remember_zaramech"	: "This Unit would be upset if you forgot she was a Zaramech.",
	"forgot_zaramech"	: "Have you really forgotten that This Unit is a Zaramech?",
	"blue_mote_o"		: "This Unit is lucky to be filled with motes of her favorite color.",
	"blue_mote_x"		: "This Unit is filled with |C3|Blue|C0| motes.",
	"senti_love_o"		: "This Unit means every word of that literally.",
	"senti_fear_o"		: "Please disregard any fear induced speech errors that may come from This Unit.",
	"senti_said_x"		: "This Unit will say \"[VAL3]\" while presenting as |C3|[VAL1].|C0|",
	
	"seriesA_00"		: {
		"question"	: "This Unit has a favorite color, what is it?",
		"correct"	: "You know This Unit so well.",
		"incorrect"	: "The favorite color of This Unit is blue.",
	},
	"seriesA_01"		: {
		"question"	: "How many fingers do you have on your left hand?",
		"correct"	: "Your ability to count the fingers on your hand is unparalleled.",
		"incorrect"	: "This Unit has now met a Zaraden with the inability to count her fingers.",
	},
	"seriesA_02"		: {
		"question"	: "How many fingers do you have on both of your hands?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit sometimes wishes she had fingers to hold things instead of only claws for violence.",
		"incorrect"	: "This Unit has now met a Zaraden with the inability to count her fingers.",
	},
	"seriesA_03"		: {
		"question"	: "How many moons orbit the planet, Eyeris?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit is glad to see the moons are still in your dreams.",
		"incorrect"	: "This Unit supposes that you have forgotten about the 3 moons behind the perpetual clouds.",
	},
	"seriesA_04"		: {
		"question"	: "What does |C3|[VAL1] times [VAL2]|C0| evaluate to?",
		"correct"	: "Multiplication is no problem for you.",
		"incorrect"	: "[VAL1] times [VAL2] evaluates to [VAL3].",
	},
	"seriesA_05"		: {
		"question"	: "What is |C3|Scrambla's|C0| favorite color?",
		"incorrect"	: "Try to remember what tetrid color gives her the most power.",
	},
	"seriesA_06"		: {
		"question"	: "What is |C3|Boiler's|C0| favorite color?",
		"incorrect"	: "Try to remember what tetrid color gives her the most power.",
	},
	"seriesA_07"		: {
		"question"	: "What is |C3|Blot's|C0| favorite color?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit was also surprised to discover that she has a favorite color.",
		"incorrect"	: "It is surprising, but try to remember what tetrid color gives her the most power.",
	},
	"seriesA_08"		: {
		"question"	: "What is |C3|Lila's|C0| favorite color?",
		"correct"	: "She says they taste like sweet fruit to her, but This Unit detects no flavor.",
		"incorrect"	: "Try to remember what tetrid color has her favorite flavor.",
	},
	"seriesA_09"		: {
		"question"	: "What is |C3|Vitrea's|C0| favorite color?",
		"correct"	: "She claims it is because of the night sky, but This Unit wonders if there is another reason.",
		"incorrect"	: "Try to remember what tetrid color gives her the most power.",
	},
	"seriesA_10"		: {
		"question"	: "What is |C3|Solara's|C0| favorite color?",
		"incorrect"	: "Try to remember what tetrid color gives her the most power.",
	},
	"seriesA_11"		: {
		"question"	: "What is |C3|Abyss'|C0| favorite color?",
		"incorrect"	: "Try to remember what tetrid color gives her the most power.",
	},
	"seriesA_12"		: {
		"question"	: "What is |C3|Blue Veyeral's|C0| favorite color?",
		"correct"	: "That was the easiest possible question in the known universe.",
		"incorrect"	: "The only possible explanation for your answer is the desire to see a comical reaction from This Unit.",
	},
	"seriesA_13"		: {
		"question"	: "When a Zaraden feels |C3|shame,|C0| what color of motes will form in her heart?",
		"incorrect"	: "Look into the memories unlocked within your radiated |C3|tetrid bonus gifts.",
	},
	"seriesA_14"		: {
		"question"	: "When a Zaraden feels |C3|frustration,|C0| what color of motes will form in her heart?",
		"incorrect"	: "Look into the memories unlocked within your radiated |C3|tetrid bonus gifts.",
	},
	"seriesA_15"		: {
		"question"	: "When a Zaraden experiences |C3|denial,|C0| what color of motes will form in her heart?",
		"incorrect"	: "Look into the memories unlocked within your radiated |C3|tetrid bonus gifts.",
	},
	"seriesA_16"		: {
		"question"	: "When a Zaraden feels |C3|anxiety,|C0| what color of motes will form in her heart?",
		"incorrect"	: "Look into the memories unlocked within your radiated |C3|tetrid bonus gifts.",
	},
	"seriesA_17"		: {
		"question"	: "When a Zaraden feels |C3|insecurity,|C0| what color of motes will form in her heart?",
		"incorrect"	: "Look into the memories unlocked within your radiated |C3|tetrid bonus gifts.",
	},
	"seriesA_18"		: {
		"question"	: "When a Zaraden feels |C3|loneliness,|C0| what color of motes will form in her heart?",
		"incorrect"	: "Look into the memories unlocked within your radiated |C3|tetrid bonus gifts.",
	},
	"seriesA_19"		: {
		"question"	: "There are |C3|[VAL1] cakes|C0| that have each been sliced into |C3|[VAL2] pieces.|C0| How many pieces are there in total?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit does not like cake, but she will share all her pieces.",
		"incorrect"	: "There are [VAL3] pieces of cake.",
	},
	"seriesA_20"		: {
		"question"	: "The Scramblas of |C3|[VAL1] universes|C0| have each eaten |C3|[VAL2] bars of soap.|C0| How many bars of soap have been eaten?",
		"correct"	: "Scrambla has a very BASIC diet.",
		"incorrect"	: "Scramblas will have eaten [VAL3] bars of soap.",
	},
	"seriesA_21"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these monsters will want to |C3|trade gifts|C0| with you if you meet them again?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL3]|C0| is the one with gifts to trade.",
	},
	"seriesA_22"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these monsters will give you |C3|free gifts|C0| if you meet them again?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL3]|C0| will give you free gifts.",
	},
	"seriesA_23"		: {
		"question"	: "Who provides the storage room for the art gallery?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Blot|C0| uses her own backroom dimension for storage.",
	},
	"seriesA_24"		: {
		"question"	: "Who provides the storage room for the observatory?",
		"correct"	: "Vitrea and Amalga are close friends.",
		"incorrect"	: "Vitrea uses |C3|Amalga's|C0| backroom dimension for storage.",
	},
	"seriesA_25"		: {
		"question"	: "Who does |C3|Glacia|C0| want to find cosmic gifts for?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit detects intentions of courtship from her actions.",
	},
	"seriesA_26"		: {
		"question"	: "When |C3|Amalga|C0| shows you her hospitality, how many gifts does she give you?",
		"correct"	: "She would give you an arm and a leg on top of that.",
	},
	"seriesA_27"		: {
		"question"	: "How many gifts does |C3|Ombroah|C0| give you when you visit her umbrella?",
	},
	"seriesA_28"		: {
		"question"	: "How many free gifts does |C3|Roundsaw|C0| give you when you visit her?",
	},
	"seriesA_29"		: {
		"question"	: "How many gifts does |C3|Burning Veyeral|C0| give you when it is time for burning?",
	},
	"seriesA_30"		: {
		"question"	: "How many |C3|free gifts|C0| does |C3|Monovai|C0| give you as revenge when you visit her again?",
		"correct"	: "|C3|Monovai|C0| only gives you gifts as a consequence for trading with her.",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Monovai|C0| does not give any gifts away for free.",
	},
	"seriesA_31"		: {
		"question"	: "How many |C3|free gifts|C0| can you receive from |C3|Prisma's Duplicator?|C0|",
		"correct"	: "|C3|Prisma's Duplicator|C0| always requires some matter to exchange.",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Prisma's Duplicator|C0| does not create any gifts for free.",
	},
	"seriesA_32"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift does |C3|Calorie|C0| want the most?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Calorie|C0| wants |C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| to help her cool off.",
	},
	"seriesA_33"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift does |C3|Frozen Veyeral|C0| want the most?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Frozen Veyeral|C0| wants |C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| to help her warm up.",
	},
	"seriesA_34"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift does |C3|Monovai|C0| want the most?",
		"correct"	: "|C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| bring the greatest consequences from |C3|Monovai.|C0|",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Monovai|C0| wants |C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| to light up the night.",
	},
	"seriesA_35"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift provides |C3|Prisma's Duplicator|C0| with the most power?",
		"correct"	: "Try harvesting free energy by recovering the |C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| you feed to the duplicator.",
	},
	"seriesA_36"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift will |C3|Calorie|C0| reject?",
		"incorrect"	: "She will reject |C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| as they will not help her cool off.",
	},
	"seriesA_37"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift will |C3|Frozen Veyeral|C0| reject?",
		"incorrect"	: "She will reject |C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| as they will not help her warm up.",
	},
	"seriesA_38"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift will |C3|Monovai|C0| reject?",
		"correct"	: "|C3|Monovai|C0| is happy to show you the repercussions of any gift.",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Monovai|C0| does not reject any type of gift.",
	},
	"seriesA_39"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift will |C3|Prisma's Duplicator|C0| reject as a source of power?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Prisma's Duplicator|C0| will accept all types of gifts as a power source.",
	},
	"seriesA_40"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the name of a |C3|Shamble|C0| battle song?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of a Shamble battle song.",
	},
	"seriesA_41"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the name of a |C3|Guardian|C0| battle song?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of a Guardian battle song.",
	},
	"seriesA_42"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the name of an |C3|Eyeric Glyph|C0| battle song?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of an Eyeric Glyph battle song.",
	},
	"seriesA_43"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the name of a |C3|Zaramech|C0| battle song?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of a Zaramech battle song.",
	},
	"seriesA_44"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the name of a |C3|Glass Flora|C0| battle song?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of a Glass Flora battle song.",
	},
	"seriesA_45"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the name of a |C3|Veyeral|C0| battle song?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of a Veyeral battle song.",
	},
	"seriesA_46"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the name of the battle song that plays during battles with |C3|Special Monsters?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of the Special Monster battle song.",
	},
	"seriesA_47"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the name of the battle song that plays during battles with |C3|Newborn Monsters?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of the Newborn Monster battle song.",
	},
	"seriesA_48"		: {
		"question"	: "This Unit is playing a song for you right now. What is the name of this song?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit believes that name fits this situation in a literal sense.",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|\"[VAL3]\"|C0| is the name of this song.",
	},
	"seriesA_49"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift does |C3|Chemory|C0| want the most?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Chemory|C0| wants to transmute |C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| into perfume the most.",
	},
	"seriesA_50"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of gift will |C3|Chemory|C0| reject?",
		"incorrect"	: "She will reject |C3|[VAL3] gifts|C0| because the electricity will disrupt her transmutation process.",
	},
	
	
	
	"seriesB_00"		: {
		"question"	: "Is |C3|\"[VAL1]\"|C0| a possible meaning of the [VAL2] glyph?",
		"correct"	: "You know the Eyeric language so well.",
		"incorrect"	: "That glyph is also hard for This Unit to decipher.",
	},
	"seriesB_01"		: {
		"question"	: "The [VAL1] glyph has several possible meanings. What is a possible meaning of the [VAL1] glyph?",
		"correct"	: "You know the Eyeric language so well.",
		"incorrect"	: "One possible meaning for [VAL1] is \"[VAL3].\"",
	},
	
	
	
	"seriesC_00"		: {
		"question"	: "Excluding any alternate forms, have you shown love to |C3|[VAL1]|C0| today?",
		"senti_o"	: "[battle_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "[forgot_sentinel]",
	},
	"seriesC_01"		: {
		"question"	: "Have you shown love to a monster of the |C3|[VAL1]|C0| type today?",
		"senti_o"	: "[remember_zaramech]",
		"senti_x"	: "[forgot_zaramech]",
	},
	"seriesC_02"		: {
		"question"	: "How many battles with monsters have you survived so far today?",
		"incorrect"	: "The amount of battles you have survived today is |C3|[VAL3].",
	},
	"seriesC_03"		: {
		"question"	: "How many battles have you fought with |C3|[VAL1]|C0| monsters today?",
		"incorrect"	: "The amount of battles you fought with [VAL1] monsters today is |C3|[VAL3].",
		"senti_o"	: "You made sure to include This Unit in your tally.",
		"senti_x"	: "Including This Unit, the amount of [VAL1] monsters you fought today is |C3|[VAL3].",
	},
	"seriesC_04"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these monsters have you loved today?",
		"incorrect"	: "You have shown love to |C3|[VAL3]|C0| today.",
		"senti_o"	: "[battle_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "You forgot what form This Unit was presenting as today, is that correct?",
	},
	"seriesC_05"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these monsters have you NOT shown love to yet today?",
		"incorrect"	: "You have not shown love to |C3|[VAL3]|C0| yet.",
		"senti_o"	: "This Unit knew that you would see through her trick question.",
		"senti_x"	: "This Unit was not presenting as |C3|[VAL3]|C0| today, therefore that form was not shown any love.",
	},
	
	
	
	"seriesD_00"		: {
		"question"	: "Who was the first monster you loved today?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit was always observing.",
		"incorrect"	: "The first monster you loved today was |C3|[VAL3].",
		"senti_o"	: "This Unit made sure to come see you first thing today.",
		"senti_x"	: "You forgot that This Unit was your first battle today?",
	},
	"seriesD_01"		: {
		"question"	: "Who did you battle most recently?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit witnessed that intense battle.",
		"incorrect"	: "You just had a battle with |C3|[VAL3].",
		"senti_o"	: "This Unit was very late and almost missed you today.",
		"senti_x"	: "[forgot_sentinel]",
	},
	"seriesD_02"		: {
		"question"	: "What did |C3|[VAL1]|C0| say to you before your battle with her?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| said \"[VAL3]\" before your battle with her.",
		"senti_o"	: "[senti_fear_o]",
		"senti_x"	: "This Unit said \"[VAL3]\" when she was feeling afraid.",
	},
	"seriesD_03"		: {
		"question"	: "What did |C3|[VAL1]|C0| say to you after showing her love?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| said \"[VAL3]\" after you showed her love.",
		"senti_o"	: "[senti_love_o]",
		"senti_x"	: "Have you forgotten that This Unit said \"[VAL3]\" earlier today?",
	},
	
	
	
	"seriesE_00"		: {
		"question"	: "How is the weather today?",
		"correct"	: "Your ability to look outside is outstanding.",
		"incorrect"	: "Have you forgotten to check the rain today?",
	},
	"seriesE_01"		: {
		"question"	: "How many helpers are following your heart in a |C3|Helper Chain|C0| right now?",
		"incorrect"	: "The amount of helpers in your helper chain is currently |C3|[VAL3].",
	},
	"seriesE_02"		: {
		"question"	: "How many panic attacks do you have right now?",
		"incorrect"	: "The amount of panic attacks you have is currently |C3|[VAL3].",
	},
	"seriesE_03"		: {
		"question"	: "Do you currently have |C3|[VAL1]|C0| as an active gift?",
	},
	"seriesE_04"		: {
		"question"	: "Have you achieved a |C3|Full Combo|C0| during any battle today?",
	},
	"seriesE_05"		: {
		"question"	: "Do you currently have any active |C3|Wonderful Power Gifts?",
	},
	"seriesE_06"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these Power Gifts do you have active right now?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL3]|C0| is one of your active Power Gifts.",
	},
	"seriesE_07"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these Power Gifts is NOT one of your active gifts?",
		"incorrect"	: "You do not have |C3|[VAL3]|C0| as an active Power Gift.",
	},
	
	
	
	"seriesF_00"		: {
		"question"	: "Is |C3|[VAL1]|C0| a monster of the |C3|[VAL2]|C0| type?",
		"senti_o"	: "[remember_zaramech]",
		"senti_x"	: "[forgot_zaramech]",
	},
	"seriesF_01"		: {
		"question"	: "Can you extract |C3|[VAL2]|C0| motes from |C3|[VAL1]?",
		"senti_o"	: "[blue_mote_o]",
		"senti_x"	: "[blue_mote_x]",
	},
	"seriesF_02"		: {
		"question"	: "What type of monster is |C3|[VAL1]?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| is a monster of the |C3|[VAL3]|C0| type.",
		"senti_o"	: "[remember_zaramech]",
		"senti_x"	: "[forgot_zaramech]",
	},
	"seriesF_03"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these monsters is of the |C3|[VAL1]|C0| type?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL3]|C0| is a monster of the |C3|[VAL1]|C0| type.",
		"senti_o"	: "[remember_zaramech]",
		"senti_x"	: "[forgot_zaramech]",
	},
	"seriesF_04"		: {
		"question"	: "What kind of motes can you extract from |C3|[VAL1]?",
		"incorrect"	: "You can extract |C3|[VAL3]|C0| motes from |C3|[VAL1].",
		"senti_o"	: "[blue_mote_o]",
		"senti_x"	: "[blue_mote_x]",
	},
	
	
	
	"seriesG_00"		: {
		"question"	: "How many eyes does |C3|Rendy|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_01"		: {
		"question"	: "How many eyes does |C3|Snowball|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_02"		: {
		"question"	: "How many petals does each of |C3|Kiwi's|C0| flowers have?",
	},
	"seriesG_03"		: {
		"question"	: "How many safety bubbles appear in |C3|Dendrohai's|C0| battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_04"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these Veyerals is NOT a part of the |C3|Veyeral Quartet?|C0|",
	},
	"seriesG_05"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these is NOT a simulacrum of |C3|Nova?|C0|",
	},
	"seriesG_06"		: {
		"question"	: "How many armored segments does |C3|Roundsaw|C0| have between her head and saw bloom tail?",
	},
	"seriesG_07"		: {
		"question"	: "How many safety bubbles are there in |C3|Rage Boiler's|C0| battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_08"		: {
		"question"	: "How many eyes does |C3|Knott|C0| have?",
		"correct"	: "You have noticed that This Unit only specified |C3|Knott,|C0| not |C3|Knot Knott|C0|",
		"incorrect"	: "Keep in mind, This Unit only specified |C3|Knott,|C0| not |C3|Knot Knott|C0|",
	},
	"seriesG_09"		: {
		"question"	: "How many segments make up |C3|Calorie's|C0| tail?",
	},
	"seriesG_10"		: {
		"question"	: "How many segments make up |C3|Joule's|C0| tail?",
	},
	"seriesG_11"		: {
		"question"	: "How many times does |C3|Lila|C0| fly away during her battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_12"		: {
		"question"	: "How many different colors of small aviocs does |C3|Shy Lila|C0| summon during her battle?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Shy Lila|C0| will summon three types of aviocs. They are green, red, and purple.",
	},
	"seriesG_13"		: {
		"question"	: "Is |C3|Sandrome|C0| the same length at any level?",
	},
	"seriesG_14"		: {
		"question"	: "Is |C3|Voladrome|C0| the same length at any level?",
	},
	"seriesG_15"		: {
		"question"	: "How many arms does |C3|Unit Lulu|C0| have during battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_16"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Prisma|C0| ever move from her starting position during battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_17"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Amalga|C0| ever move from her starting position during battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_18"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Rage Prisma|C0| ever move from her starting position during battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_19"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Syncron's|C0| panic form always fire all four lasers at any level?",
		"incorrect"	: "Low level |C3|Syncron|C0| will only fire two lasers in panic mode.",
	},
	"seriesG_20"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Alter Syncron's|C0| panic form always fire all four lasers at any level?",
	},
	"seriesG_21"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Flip Flap's|C0| wire length change based on their level?",
	},
	"seriesG_22"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Default|C0| choose her forms at random?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Default|C0| chooses her forms based on what level she is.",
	},
	"seriesG_23"		: {
		"question"	: "How many different hologram forms can |C3|Default|C0| project?",
	},
	"seriesG_24"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Photoxai|C0| hold your combo for the entire battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_25"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Lavalin|C0| hold your combo for the entire battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_26"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Heliola|C0| hold your combo for the entire battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_27"		: {
		"question"	: "How many feather rings does |C3|Hematoren|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_28"		: {
		"question"	: "How many feather rings does |C3|Ombroah|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_29"		: {
		"question"	: "How many small glyph orbs can |C3|Hadesoh|C0| absorb?",
	},
	"seriesG_30"		: {
		"question"	: "How many small glyph orbs can |C3|Chemory|C0| absorb?",
	},
	"seriesG_31"		: {
		"question"	: "How many small glyph orbs can |C3|Astrayo|C0| absorb?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Astrayo|C0| will not absorb any of her small glyph orbs.",
	},
	"seriesG_32"		: {
		"question"	: "Can |C3|Monovai|C0| rain blood from above?",
	},
	"seriesG_33"		: {
		"question"	: "Can |C3|Monovai|C0| rain blood from below?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Monovai|C0| will only rain blood from above.",
	},
	"seriesG_34"		: {
		"question"	: "How many breakable petals does |C3|Dot|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_35"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Glacia|C0| have more petals at higher levels?",
	},
	"seriesG_36"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Null Glacia|C0| rain void bullets upon you during her battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_37"		: {
		"question"	: "How many breakable spark thorns does |C3|Vitrea|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_38"		: {
		"question"	: "How many segments make up |C3|Pearl's|C0| tail vine?",
	},
	"seriesG_39"		: {
		"question"	: "How many |C3|Murder Blossoms|C0| dance around |C3|Momo|C0| in the ring closest to her?",
	},
	"seriesG_40"		: {
		"question"	: "How many petals do each of |C3|Shy Momo's|C0| golden blooms have?",
	},
	"seriesG_41"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Echo|C0| have more petals at higher levels?",
	},
	"seriesG_42"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Split Veyeral|C0| initially split into four Veyerals at any level?",
	},
	"seriesG_43"		: {
		"question"	: "How many small bullets orbit around |C3|Burning Veyeral's|C0| large fire rock attacks?",
	},
	"seriesG_44"		: {
		"question"	: "How many small bullets orbit around |C3|Venom Veyeral's|C0| large toxic rock attacks?",
	},
	"seriesG_45"		: {
		"question"	: "How many smaller Veyerals split out of |C3|Molten Veyeral|C0| at the start of her second phase?",
	},
	"seriesG_46"		: {
		"question"	: "How many phases does |C3|The Void's|C0| battle have?",
	},
	"seriesG_47"		: {
		"question"	: "How many phases does |C3|Totaria's|C0| battle have before she surrounds you with walls on all sides?",
	},
	"seriesG_48"		: {
		"question"	: "How many smaller Veyerals surround you at the end of |C3|Blue Veyeral's|C0| battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_49"		: {
		"question"	: "Can |C3|Veyeral Rain|C0| attack with void spikes?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Veyeral Rain|C0| will only attack with zap spikes.",
	},
	"seriesG_50"		: {
		"question"	: "How many safety bubbles are there in |C3|Frozen Veyeral's|C0| battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_51"		: {
		"question"	: "How many phases does |C3|Anomaly's|C0| battle have?",
	},
	"seriesG_52"		: {
		"question"	: "How many breakable prongs does |C3|Stella|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_53"		: {
		"question"	: "How many breakable gems does |C3|Celestia|C0| have orbiting around her?",
	},
	"seriesG_54"		: {
		"question"	: "How many wings does |C3|Unity|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_55"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Duality|C0| hold your combo when they start colliding together?",
	},
	"seriesG_56"		: {
		"question"	: "How many segments does each of |C3|Trinity's|C0| bodies have between their two heads?",
	},
	"seriesG_57"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Nix Polyps|C0| have the |ah| glyph imprinted upon her?",
	},
	"seriesG_58"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Tox Polyps|C0| have the |ry| glyph imprinted upon her?",
	},
	"seriesG_59"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Shiny Joule|C0| summon |xai| glyphs during her battle?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit wonders why Photoxai allows Joule to borrow her |xai| glyphs, even in a dream.",
	},
	"seriesG_60"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Shiny Joule|C0| summon |ren| glyphs during her battle?",
		"correct"	: "This Unit wonders why Photoxai allows Joule to borrow her |xai| glyphs, even in a dream.",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Shiny Joule|C0| summons |xai| glyphs, not |ren| glyphs.",
	},
	"seriesG_61"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these monsters can attack with thorned vines?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL3]|C0| is a monster that can attack with thorned vines.",
	},
	"seriesG_62"		: {
		"question"	: "Which group of Veyerals will ask you to show them another dream?",
	},
	"seriesG_63"		: {
		"question"	: "How many legs does |C3|Shiny Rendy|C0| have?",
		"incorrect"	: "All forms of |C3|Rendy|C0| have 4 legs.",
	},
	"seriesG_64"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these monsters will summon small |C3|aviocs|C0| during battle?",
		"incorrect"	: "This Unit supposes you may have forgotten that |C3|aviocs|C0| are small flying eyeball creatures.",
	},
	"seriesG_65"		: {
		"question"	: "How many times must the love bar be filled to completely destroy |C3|Shiny Anomaly's|C0| rock shell?",
	},
	"seriesG_66"		: {
		"question"	: "How many smaller Veyerals split out of |C3|Storm Veyeral|C0| at the start of her second phase?",
	},
	"seriesG_67"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Chionotoh|C0| hold your combo for the entire battle?",
	},
	"seriesG_68"		: {
		"question"	: "In order to attract |C3|Philolu's|C0| attention, how many other Eyeric Glyphs must be loved first?",
		"correct"	: "|C3|Philolu|C0| is extremely picky, so you must be very special.",
	},
	"seriesG_69"		: {
		"question"	: "How many Eyeric Glyphs are imprinted upon |C3|Ventra's|C0| mechanical heart?",
		"correct"	: "Many Zaramechs have their own name imprinted on their heart drive.",
		"incorrect"	: "One of the symbols imprinted on |C3|Ventra's|C0| mechanical heart is not an Eyeric Glyph.",
	},
	"seriesG_70"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|Guardian Soul|C0| always drop your combo if you let any breakable parts escape?",
		"incorrect"	: "Guardian Soul will only drop your combo if a |C3|white soul fragment|C0| escapes.",
	},
	"seriesG_71"		: {
		"question"	: "How many eyes orbit around |C3|Shiny Knot|C0| at the start of her battle?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|Shiny Knot|C0| will only bring her eyes out after |C3|Shiny Knott|C0| appears.",
	},
	"seriesG_72"		: {
		"question"	: "How many |C3|Shiny Syncron|C0| units can be golden at once?",
	},
	"seriesG_73"		: {
		"question"	: "How many breakable parts does |C3|Shanx|C0| have on her legs?",
		"incorrect"	: "There are 2 breakable parts on each of |C3|Shanx's|C0| legs.",
	},
	"seriesG_74"		: {
		"question"	: "How many eyes does |C3|Alter Shanx|C0| have?",
	},
	"seriesG_75"		: {
		"question"	: "Which of these monsters has NO eyes in battle?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL3]|C0| is a monster with no eyes.",
	},
	
	
	
	"seriesH_00"		: {
		"question"	: "Can |C3|[VAL1]|C0| attack with the |C3|[VAL2]|C0| element?",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "[wrong_sentinel]",
	},
	"seriesH_01"		: {
		"question"	: "Does |C3|[VAL1]|C0| have a weakness to the |C3|[VAL2]|C0| element?",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "[wrong_sentinel]",
	},
	"seriesH_02"		: {
		"question"	: "Is |C3|[VAL1]|C0| resistant against the |C3|[VAL2]|C0| element?",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "[wrong_sentinel]",
	},
	"seriesH_03"		: {
		"question"	: "What is an element that |C3|[VAL1]|C0| can attack with?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| can attack with |C3|[VAL3].",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "In that form, This Unit can attack with |C3|[VAL3].",
	},
	"seriesH_04"		: {
		"question"	: "What is an element that |C3|[VAL1]|C0| has a weakness against?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| is weak to |C3|[VAL3].",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "In that form, This Unit is weak to |C3|[VAL3].",
	},
	"seriesH_05"		: {
		"question"	: "What is an element that |C3|[VAL1]|C0| is resistant to?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| can resist |C3|[VAL3].",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "In that form, This Unit will resist |C3|[VAL3].",
	},
	
	
	
	"seriesI_00"		: {
		"question"	: "Can |C3|[VAL1]|C0| have a |C3|level [VAL2]|C0| battle without being overleveled or underleveled?",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "[wrong_sentinel]",
	},
	"seriesI_01"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the lowest level that |C3|[VAL1]|C0| can reach without being underleveled?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| can be as low as |C3|[VAL3]|C0| without being underleveled.",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "In that form, This Unit can be as low as |C3|[VAL3]|C0| without being underleveled.",
	},
	"seriesI_02"		: {
		"question"	: "What is the highest level that |C3|[VAL1]|C0| can reach without being overleveled?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| can reach up to |C3|[VAL3]|C0| without being overleveled.",
		"senti_o"	: "[correct_sentinel]",
		"senti_x"	: "In that form, This Unit can reach up to |C3|[VAL3]|C0| without being overleveled.",
	},
	"seriesI_03"		: {
		"question"	: "What does |C3|[VAL1]|C0| say to you before the start of a battle?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| says \"[VAL3]\" before you battle her.",
		"senti_o"	: "[senti_fear_o]",
		"senti_x"	: "[senti_said_x]",
	},
	"seriesI_04"		: {
		"question"	: "What does |C3|[VAL1]|C0| say to you after showing her love?",
		"incorrect"	: "|C3|[VAL1]|C0| says \"[VAL3]\" after you love her.",
		"senti_o"	: "[senti_love_o]",
		"senti_x"	: "[senti_said_x]",
	},
	
	
	
	"ans_nothing"		: "Nothing",
	"ans_0"				: "None",
	"ans_1"				: "One",
	"ans_2"				: "Two",
	"ans_3"				: "Three",
	"ans_4"				: "Four",
	"ans_5"				: "Five",
	"ans_6"				: "Six",
	"ans_7"				: "Seven",
	"ans_8"				: "Eight",
	"ans_9"				: "Nine",
	"ans_10"			: "Ten",
	"ans_11"			: "Eleven",
	"ans_12"			: "Twelve",
	
	"ans_level"			: "Lv [VAL1]",
	
	"ans_maybe1"		: "I think so?",
	"ans_maybe2"		: "Probably?",
	"ans_maybe3"		: "Does [VAL1] count?",
	"ans_type_maybe1"	: "Sort of a [VAL1]",
	"ans_type_maybe2"	: "Kinda like a [VAL1]",
	"ans_maybe_gem"		: "Maybe [VAL1]",
	
	"2_elements"		: "[VAL1] and [VAL2]",
	"3_elements"		: "[VAL1], [VAL2], and [VAL3]",
	"4_elements"		: "[VAL1], [VAL2], [VAL3] and [VAL4]",
	
	"glyph_answers"	: {
		"ans_soh_1"		: "Fire",
		"ans_soh_2"		: "Passion",
		"ans_soh_3"		: "Warmth",
		"ans_ah_1"		: "Water",
		"ans_ah_2"		: "Rain",
		"ans_ah_3"		: "Darkness",
		"ans_vai_1"		: "Space",
		"ans_vai_2"		: "Vacant",
		"ans_vai_3"		: "Lonely",
		"ans_ren_1"		: "Blood",
		"ans_ren_2"		: "Life",
		"ans_ren_3"		: "Soul",
		"ans_ai_1"		: "Self",
		"ans_ai_2"		: "New",
		"ans_ai_3"		: "Clean",
		"ans_xai_1"		: "Light",
		"ans_xai_2"		: "Glowing",
		"ans_xai_3"		: "Brightness",
		"ans_ry_1"		: "Chemical",
		"ans_ry_2"		: "Element",
		"ans_ry_3"		: "Nature",
		"ans_yo_1"		: "Lightning",
		"ans_yo_2"		: "Energy",
		"ans_yo_3"		: "Excitement",
		"ans_lin_1"		: "Chaos",
		"ans_lin_2"		: "Destruction",
		"ans_lin_3"		: "Liquify",
		"ans_la_1"		: "Star",
		"ans_la_2"		: "Time",
		"ans_la_3"		: "Roundness",
		"ans_hai_1"		: "Plant",
		"ans_hai_2"		: "Distance",
		"ans_hai_3"		: "Growth",
		"ans_toh_1"		: "Frozen",
		"ans_toh_2"		: "Cold",
		"ans_toh_3"		: "Stillness",
		"ans_lu_1"		: "Love",
		"ans_lu_2"		: "Heart",
		"ans_lu_3"		: "Core",
		"ans_ral_1"		: "Everything",
		"ans_ral_2"		: "Category",
		"ans_ral_3"		: "Connection",
	},
	
	"take_reward" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"random"			: 4,
			"dialog_rand1"		: "This is clearly the optimal choice.",
			"dialog_rand2"		: "This is the most correct choice.",
			"dialog_rand3"		: "Your knowledge has earned you this gift.",
			"dialog_rand4"		: "This Unit successfully predicted that you would choose this gift.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "You may proceed to another round of questions if you wish.",
		},
	],
	
	"dont_play" 	: [
		{
			"play_music"		: "silence",
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_sad"],
			"dialog"			: "Oh... This Unit understands.|L||!|There are more important things to do.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_upset"],
			"dialog"			: "|C3|Pain detected|C0|",
		},
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "Right! You will just play This Unit's game at a later time.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit loves you.",
		},
	],
	
	"round1_start" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit will now ask you a series of questions.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "The joy in This Unit cannot be contained within this shell.",
		},
	],
	
	"round1_clear" 	: [
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "That is |C3|Correct!",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "[VAL1]",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "You have successfully answered four questions correctly.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit is |shake|jittering|norm| with excitement.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit will now present you with your reward.",
		},
	],
	
	"round2_start" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit will now continue with more difficult questions.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit is now |shake|vibrating|norm| with excitement.",
		},
	],
	
	"round2_clear" 	: [
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "That is |C3|Correct!",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "[VAL1]",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "You have successfully completed |C3|Round Two.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "It is almost impossible to contain the bliss that This Unit is feeling.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit will now present you with another reward.",
		},
	],
	
	"round3_start" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit will now present you with the most difficult questions that she could create today.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "It is now |shake|actually impossible|norm| to contain the bliss that This Unit is feeling.",
		},
	],
	
	"round3_clear" 	: [
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "That is |C3|Correct!",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "[VAL1]",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "You have successfully completed |C3|The Final Round.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "There is a non-zero chance that This Unit will explode at any moment.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit must now congratulate you on completing her game.",
		},
	],
	
	"strike_out" 	: [
		{
			"play_music"		: "silence",
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_sad"],
			"dialog"			: "That is |shake||C4|Incorrect.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_confused"],
			"dialog"			: "[VAL1]",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_sad"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit regrets to inform you that you have accumulated three strikes.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_confused"],
			"dialog"			: "This means that the game must end here.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "Please accept this hug as a consolation prize.",
		},
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"random"			: 3,
			"dialog_rand1"		: "This Unit loves you.",
			"dialog_rand2"		: "This Unit will now begin processing this hug.",
			"dialog_rand3"		: "This Unit predicts that you will get them next time.",
		},
	],
	
	
	"victory_blank" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_blank", "CHAR_blank_left", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "I had so much fun, Sentinel.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit is requesting a hug before you leave.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_blank", "CHAR_blank_left", "MOOD_very_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "|wave|I love you!",
		},
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "|C3|Sensory Overload|C0|",
		},
	],
	
	"victory_defect" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_defect", "CHAR_defect_left", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "Those questions were fun today!",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_veyeral", "CHAR_blue_veyeral_left", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "Although, there could stand to be a few more questions about me, Blue Veyeral.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_confused"],
			"dialog"			: "Perhaps there will be more next time.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit is requesting a hug before you leave.",
		},
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit will now process this hug for the next few hours.",
		},
	],
	
	"victory_twins" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_ryden", "CHAR_ryden_left", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "Isn't my sister a genius?",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_xaila", "CHAR_xaila_left", "MOOD_blush"],
			"dialog"			: "Oh, I'm just good at remembering things.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_xaila", "CHAR_xaila_left", "MOOD_angry"],
			"dialog"			: "Wait! |shake|You didn't help at all!",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit is impressed beyond the scope of possible measurement.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_ryden", "CHAR_ryden_left", "MOOD_suspicious2"],
			"dialog"			: "See, Sunshine?|L||!||wave|She likes smart girls.",
		},
	],
	
	"victory_devil" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_devil", "CHAR_devil_left", "MOOD_very_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "Ha! I have conquered your quiz!",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_devil", "CHAR_devil_left", "MOOD_aggressive2"],
			"dialog"			: "You should know that I, The Devil, can't be defeated so easily!",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_devil", "CHAR_devil_left", "MOOD_content"],
			"dialog"			: "But I admire how hard you tried, so I'll just have to give you a prize anyways.",
		},
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "|C3|Sensory Overload|C0|",
		},
	],
	
	"victory_default" 	: [
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "Enjoy the gift that your knowledge has brought upon you.",
		},
		{
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_normal"],
			"dialog"			: "This Unit is requesting a hug before you leave.",
		},
		{
			"love_hearts"		: 1,
			"character"			: ["VOICE_sentinel", "CHAR_sentinel_right", "MOOD_happy"],
			"dialog"			: "|C3|Sensory Overload|C0|",
		},
	],

}